<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN: S.A.R.A.H. ranger-class aviators -->
  <US_AviatorGlasses.label>S.A.R.A.H. ranger-class aviators</US_AviatorGlasses.label>
  <!-- EN: A pair of large sunglasses, typically associated with security and military personnel. This pair of aviators are more useful than they first seem however, as they are fitted with a S.A.R.A.H. (short for Semi-Autonomic Reconnaissance and Acquisition of Hostiles) subpersona AI. This AI's primary directive is to mark and track targets to help the wearer land more accurate shots. This focus on accuracy pushes these glasses to be superior to a S.A.M. class AI in terms of accuracy, in exchange for a slight delay in targeting and thus a small delay in aiming time. It has a secondary function that analyzes the terrain around the wearer and inform them of any obstacles in their way, facilitating faster movement.\n\nThese glasses also have a PLATE class shield generator built in that fully envelops the wearer's head. It acts similarly to standard armor, as while it does not provide perfect protection, it will never break from heat buildup, nor does it get in the way of projectile weaponry. The shield is also invisible, because having a giant bubble around the user's head would be a crime against fashion. Due to the fact that these shades are explicitly designed for combat, the shield generator is strengthened at the cost of being more expensive to produce. -->
  <US_AviatorGlasses.description>A pair of large sunglasses, typically associated with security and military personnel. This pair of aviators are more useful than they first seem however, as they are fitted with a S.A.R.A.H. (short for Semi-Autonomic Reconnaissance and Acquisition of Hostiles) subpersona AI. This AI's primary directive is to mark and track targets to help the wearer land more accurate shots. This focus on accuracy pushes these glasses to be superior to a S.A.M. class AI in terms of accuracy, in exchange for a slight delay in targeting and thus a small delay in aiming time. It has a secondary function that analyzes the terrain around the wearer and inform them of any obstacles in their way, facilitating faster movement.

These glasses also have a PLATE class shield generator built in that fully envelops the wearer's head. It acts similarly to standard armor, as while it does not provide perfect protection, it will never break from heat buildup, nor does it get in the way of projectile weaponry. The shield is also invisible, because having a giant bubble around the user's head would be a crime against fashion. Due to the fact that these shades are explicitly designed for combat, the shield generator is strengthened at the cost of being more expensive to produce.</US_AviatorGlasses.description>
</LanguageData>
