<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN: ATLAS psyker-class shades -->
  <US_PsykerShades.label>ATLAS psyker-class shades</US_PsykerShades.label>
  <!-- EN: A pair of striking and alluring shades. The awe-inspiring appearance of these sunglasses reflects the powers contained within them. This pair of shades is not installed with a subpersona AI like other pairs of sunglasses. It is instead based on a blueprint from the mechanoid wars from a secret operation apparently called Project ATLAS. The internal structure of these glasses is made of an experimental alloy between eltex and architect material, providing both incredible durability and peerless psionic enhancement to its wearer.\n\nHowever, this is not the most fascinating ability of these glasses. Project ATLAS figured out how to manipulate certain psychic artifacts into a built in weapon. ATLAS shades accumulate and store a large amount of psionic energy over time. When enough energy is built up, the user can enter into a brief trance like state and cast a powerful explosive bolt of psionic gravitational energy at a target, shredding and then crushing anyone unlucky enough to get caught in the blast.\n        \nThese glasses also generate a miniature psychic shield around the wearer's head. It does not block bullets like a normal shield belt, but instead acts more like conventional armor. It is tougher than any PLATE class shield generator, and seems to be more sturdy the more well made the glasses are. The shield is invisible, like the people that designed it knew that having a giant bubble around the user's head would be a crime against fashion. This bubble is also capable of resisting the vacuum of space. -->
  <US_PsykerShades.description>A pair of striking and alluring shades. The awe-inspiring appearance of these sunglasses reflects the powers contained within them. This pair of shades is not installed with a subpersona AI like other pairs of sunglasses. It is instead based on a blueprint from the mechanoid wars from a secret operation apparently called Project ATLAS. The internal structure of these glasses is made of an experimental alloy between eltex and architect material, providing both incredible durability and peerless psionic enhancement to its wearer.

However, this is not the most fascinating ability of these glasses. Project ATLAS figured out how to manipulate certain psychic artifacts into a built in weapon. ATLAS shades accumulate and store a large amount of psionic energy over time. When enough energy is built up, the user can enter into a brief trance like state and cast a powerful explosive bolt of psionic gravitational energy at a target, shredding and then crushing anyone unlucky enough to get caught in the blast.
        
These glasses also generate a miniature psychic shield around the wearer's head. It does not block bullets like a normal shield belt, but instead acts more like conventional armor. It is tougher than any PLATE class shield generator, and seems to be more sturdy the more well made the glasses are. The shield is invisible, like the people that designed it knew that having a giant bubble around the user's head would be a crime against fashion. This bubble is also capable of resisting the vacuum of space.</US_PsykerShades.description>
</LanguageData>
