<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!-- EN: V.E.N.U.S. noble-class monocle -->
  <US_RoyalEye.label>V.E.N.U.S. noble-class monocle</US_RoyalEye.label>
  <!-- EN: A incredibly beautiful and ornate monocle, typically associated with the high royalty on glitterworlds. However, this monocle is even more wondrous than it first appears, as it is fitted with a V.E.N.U.S. (short for Vanity, Empathy, Negotiation, and Urbane Specialist) subpersona AI. This AI is filled with various psychology studies and notes on various cultures, and uses this information to advise the wearer. The main features of the V.E.N.U.S. AI is improving etiquette by pointing out and correcting flaws, having a direct feed to the local market to assist with bartering, and determining the best way of breaking down or convincing a prisoner. Also of note is the use of psychic threads to enhance the user's psychic abilities.\n        \nThese glasses also have a weak PLATE class shield generator built in that fully envelops the wearer's head. It acts similarly to standard armor, as while it does not provide perfect protection, it will never break from heat buildup, nor does it get in the way of projectile weaponry. The shield is also invisible, because having a giant bubble around the user's head would be a crime against fashion. Due to the fact that these shades are not at all built for combat and are more for vanity, the shield generator in this monocle is weaker than any other pair of enhanced glasses. -->
  <US_RoyalEye.description>A incredibly beautiful and ornate monocle, typically associated with the high royalty on glitterworlds. However, this monocle is even more wondrous than it first appears, as it is fitted with a V.E.N.U.S. (short for Vanity, Empathy, Negotiation, and Urbane Specialist) subpersona AI. This AI is filled with various psychology studies and notes on various cultures, and uses this information to advise the wearer. The main features of the V.E.N.U.S. AI is improving etiquette by pointing out and correcting flaws, having a direct feed to the local market to assist with bartering, and determining the best way of breaking down or convincing a prisoner. Also of note is the use of psychic threads to enhance the user's psychic abilities.
        
These glasses also have a weak PLATE class shield generator built in that fully envelops the wearer's head. It acts similarly to standard armor, as while it does not provide perfect protection, it will never break from heat buildup, nor does it get in the way of projectile weaponry. The shield is also invisible, because having a giant bubble around the user's head would be a crime against fashion. Due to the fact that these shades are not at all built for combat and are more for vanity, the shield generator in this monocle is weaker than any other pair of enhanced glasses.</US_RoyalEye.description>
</LanguageData>
